真不敢相信你们还在盯着那看
I can't believe you guys are still staring over there!
现在很多人选择持续喂母乳到孩子更大
Some other's tend to breast feed for a lot longer for these days,
这叫"亲密育儿法"
it's called the "attachment parenting".
孩子那么大了 应该叫"亲密约会法"吧
When the kids that big, it's called "dating".
而且他总得伸出头来喘口气吧
I mean, he's gotta come up for air at some point.
没必要
No, he doesn't.
他过了直接奶头喝奶的年龄很久了吧
Isn't he too old to drink from the tit?
那小孩就我这么高
The kid is my height.
想都不要想
Don't get any ideas.
这事还真发生了 我果然活太久了
Well, it's happened: I've lived too long.
服务员 我要点餐
Miss, I'm ready to order.
我不想去 我能尊重这种做法
I can't. I mean, I respect it all,
但我会恶心想吐的
but I'll throw up.
我去好了 交不起钱看HBO台
I'll go. I can't afford HBO,
《权利的游戏》中的乱伦戏码
and it's the closest I can get
只能现在看了
to seeing Game of Thrones.
你好 请问要点什么
Hi, what can I get you?
显然他已经在喝着饮料了
He's obviously good drink-wise.
我要杯茶和一个火鸡培根三明治
I'll have tea and a turkey club.
那他要什么 需要给"奶"加点咖啡吗
Anything for him? Coffee for the milk?
汉堡还是薯条
Burger? Fries?
薯条好了
I'll have fries.
哇 大半夜还有电话
Ooh! Late night phone call.
找人午夜寻欢哟
Ring-a-ding-dang.
有人要胡搞瞎搞啦
Someone's gonna get their freaky freak on.
是我爸啦
It's my father.
我很开明的
I don't judge.
爸爸
Hey, daddy.
我很好呀
Me? I'm fine.
有点失望 现在是松露季节
A little bummed: It's truffle season,
而这里却没人知道松露是什么
and no one I know knows what a truffle is,
不过
but...
我们的财产拍卖会吗
Oh! Our estate auction?
知道啊 我是有听说过
Yeah, I think I heard something about that.
但老实说 爸爸 我一点都不放在心上
But honestly, daddy, I haven't given it a second thought.
不 你不必担心我
No, you don't have to worry about me.
我情绪平和 一点也不激动
I am not at all emotional about it.
这...
Wha--
幸好今天不是周五拖鞋上班日
Thank God it's not flip-flop Friday.
等等 我问她
Well, wait, I'll ask her.
我老爸想请你跟我一起去监狱见他
My father wants to know if you'll come out to the prison
-然后大家见一面 -没问题
- and finally meet him. - Sure.
很好 那我们明天见
Great. We'll see you tomorrow.
再见
Bye.
我不才不去
I'm not going.
为什么 那你刚才还答应他
What? Why'd you say yes?
不可以拒绝在牢里的人啊
'cause you never tell a man in prison no.
他会用皮带上吊自尽的
He could hang himself with his belt.
别用那种眼神看我
Do not give me that look.
我已经碰过两次了
It happened to me twice already.
拜托哦 什么事情你没碰过两次啊
Oh, God, has anything not happened to you twice already?
求你了 麦克斯 你能跟我的父亲见面
Max, come on. It's really important to me
对我来说很重要
that you meet my father.
你也没见过我爹
Well, you never met my father,
我也没有拉着你
and you don't see me dragging you
试图去全国所有的货运火车上找他啊
to every railroad boxcar in the country trying to find him.
求你了 这周我已经够不顺心了
Come on, it's gonna be a really hard week for me.
你有哪一周是顺心的吗
Has any week ever not been hard for you?
我过去拥有的一切东西
Everything I've ever owned
通通要被拿去拍卖给社会大众了
is being auctioned off to the public.
我颜面无存
I'm humiliated.
那想必现在不是个告诉你
Would this be a bad time to tell you
你那根超长脸毛又长出来的好时机
your one long face hair is back?
看来有些东西是他们抢不走
Well, there's something they can't take away from me,
而我自己也拔不掉的
and apparently, I can't either.
哎哟 哎哟 阳光美女驾到
Well, well, here comes the sun,
身后两轮丰臀也美丽动人
and the moon is looking great too.
厄尔 你那七分调戏 外加三分挑逗
Oh, Earl, your flirting is just the right amount of dirty,
总是如此恰到好处
and that's not easy.
苏菲来了 帮我看下我的发罩
Sophie's here. Quick, how's my hairnet?
我要过去邀请她与我共赴一场
I'm about to go over and ask her out
浪漫约会
on a romantic date.
约会 这不是脱裤子放屁吗
A date? Isn't that a waste of time?
你们两个的上床次数
I mean, you guys already have sex so often,
比我验孕次数还频繁
I took a pregnancy test.
晚上好啊 苏菲
Evening, Sophie.
如你所知 我们一共做过
As you know, we have now been together
468次的"床上运动"
for 468 sexual encounters.
我想也该是时候 带你来一次浪漫约会了
I believe it is time I take you out on a romantic date.
我不知道呢
Aw, I don't know.
这年头谁还有空出去约会啊
Who has time to go out anymore?
你就跟平常一样 来我家
Can't you just come over and ruin my sheets
"滚乱"我的床单就好啦
like you usually do?
你就答应我嘛
Oh, just say yes.
你想去哪里我都带你去
I'll take you anywhere you want.
那就带我去钱宁家的拍卖会
Then take me to the Channing family auction
给我买点金子做的东西
and buy me something gold.
这哪里浪漫了
How is this romantic?
这哪里不浪漫
有金子就浪漫啊
It's gold.
那不是卡洛琳家财产拍卖会的目录吗
Wait, is that the catalog from Caroline 's estate auction?
是的
Yes.
我在我们大楼外的垃圾堆看到的
I found it in the trash out behind our building.
那是卡洛琳扔的 因为她不想再看到
Caroline threw it there 'cause she doesn't wanna see it again.
你最好赶紧给我 不然等会她出来看到
You better give it to me before she comes out here
会放火烧你的 她最近有这癖好
and lights you on fire. She kinda does that now.
苏菲 快放手
Sophie, let go, seriously.
麦克斯 你赢不了我
No, you're never gonna win, Max.
我出生时 医生费了好大的劲
You know, when I was born, the doctors tried
也撬不开我攥在手里死去的那双胞姐妹
to pry my dead twin sister from my hands,
但我怎么都不放手
but I never let go.
于是她成了我第一个娃娃
She was my first doll.
苏菲 你身上有带拔毛夹子吗
Hey, Sophie, you don't happen to have any tweezers, do you?
就是那种很好用的工业拔毛夹
Like, the really good industrial kind?
你也知道你的那根毛啊
Oh, you know about the hair?
本来还想带你去喝个酒
'Cause I was gonna have to take you out for a beer
然后趁你喝醉时告诉你呢
and talk about it.
麦克斯 你身后藏着的是什么啊
Max, what is that thing that you have behind your back?
什么 没有啊
What? No, nothing.
有啊 就在这里
Yes, right here.
刚从你双腿之间落下的
Is that the auction catalog
是我家拍卖会的目录吗
that just fell between your legs?
不是 你是在看现场版的
No, you're watching an episode
《糊涂妈妈进产房》
of I didn't know I was pregnant.
为什么这会在这里
What is this thing doing here?
我有根两英尺长的脸毛还不够惨吗
Isn't it enough I have a 2-foot face hair?
干得好啊 阿憨 她又不开心了
Nice, Han. She's upset again. Happy?
抱歉 我还以为在玩你藏我找的游戏
Sorry, I thought we were playing some kind of hiding game.
你下次再这样
Oh, reach for me like that again
我就跟你玩另一个游戏
and we'll be playing a different game
叫做"猜猜我又砍下阿憨身上哪个部位"
called "Guess which part of Han I cut off."
你们学乖就好
Yeah, that's right.
还不赶紧滚蛋
You better walk away.
我可以拿回我的目录了吗
Now, can I have my catalog back?
是你带进来的啊
You brought this in here?
我真不敢相信 苏菲
I can't believe it, Sophie.
你觉得坐在这里 随意翻阅
I can't believe you think it's okay for you
我家以前的财产目录合适吗
to just sit here and casually flip through this catalog
我以前所有珍爱的东西都在里面啊
that contains everything I love from my old life.
也太不考虑一下别人心情了
I just think it's really insensitive and stuff.
你脑子里想什么啊
I mean, what are you thinking?
你是怎么回事啊
What is wrong with you,
更别说你这身
I mean, besides your obvious choice
丑色的烂衣服了
of bad fabric and color.
你好样的
Oh, no.
你给我闪开点 长毛女
You back up your truck, bearded lady.
我不考虑别人心情吗
I'm insensitive?
是我偷了全城人的钱吗
I'm the thief who stole all those people's money?
你难道看不出这配色能衬托我的美貌吗
And you don't think this color is happening?
去买本波兰版《时尚》杂志学学吧
Pick up a copy of Polish Vogue.
好了 好了 够了
All right, okay, okay.
这有点太剑拔弩张了
It's all getting a little tense.
我想大家心知肚明
I think we're all clear
该怎么样解除这尴尬场面
about what needs to happen right now.
我拔
Plink.
这个监狱比上次那个好太多了
Wow, this prison's a lot better than the last one.
简直就像乡村俱乐部
It's more like a country club.
签到的时候 我好像看到了不少混双球员名单
I mean, I think I saw a list for mixed doubles where we signed in.
麦克斯 我知道你觉得森林里的弃置车辆
Max, I know your idea of a country club's
也算是乡村俱乐部
an abandoned car in the woods,
但你看这里
but look around.
有监视器 跟加了铁网的窗子呢
There's security cameras and bars on the windows.
好嘛 这是一间硬汉乡村俱乐部
All right, so it's a rough country club,
强壮高球员会把杆弟当小妞搞
where the strongest golfers make the caddies their bitch.
麦克斯 我爸爸是在坐牢
Max, my father's in prison.
考虑一下人家心情什么的嘛
Be more sensitive and stuff.
我懂 他是你亲爹
Look, I get it. You're protective.
你护着他 你爱他
He's your father and you love him,
但不是大家都会这么觉得啊
but I'm sorry, not everybody feels that way.
-老爸 -乖女儿
- Daddy. - There she is.
-我的乖女最近好吗 -挺好啊 老爸
- How's my little girl? - I'm great, daddy.
你这套新制服不错哦
Yeah. I like the new uniform,
完全没有囚服的感觉
and it isn't at all prison-y.
我也不知道哪样比较惨 是被关在监狱呢
Yeah. I don't know what's worse: being locked up
还是穿的像香蕉共和国店员一样呢
or looking like you work at a Banana Republic.
等等 你不会就是麦克斯吧
Now, wait a minute. This can't be Max.
以前听你的事 我还以为你会是
The stories I've heard, I was expecting more
卡车司机型的猛女呢
of a truck driver.
布莱恩 你头先别过去吧
Hey, Brian, you might wanna look the other way.
麦克斯是来带我越狱的
I think Max is here to break me out.
对吧 麦克斯
Isn't that right, Max?
真会说笑 马丁·钱宁
Martin Channing.
请坐吧
Shall we?
好啦 你爹棒呆了
Okay, fine, your dad is awesome.
我们小蛋糕生意的预期增长比
Well, our projected cupcake business growth ratio
虽然还没达到目标 但秋季马上要到了
isn't where I want it to be, but with autumn here,
我们很看好要推出的新产品
We have a lot of hope in the launch
南瓜香料口味小蛋糕
of our new pumpkin spice flavor.
宝贝 我很爱你
Honey, I love you very much,
但我们时间不多
but we're almost out of time,
我没时间听你多说小蛋糕了
and I can't talk anymore about cupcakes.
想听听你的意见嘛
Just wanted to pick your brain.
麦克斯 今天请你来
Now, Max, I asked you to meet me here today
是想请你帮我个忙
because I wanna ask you a favor.
是想我偷带东西进来吗
You want me to smuggle something in?
还是要偷带出去 两项我都是高手
Something out? I'm good either way.
我想请你带卡洛琳去财产拍卖会
I want you to take Caroline to the estate auction.
老爸 不要
Daddy, no.
为什么要我去承受那些痛苦
Why would I put myself through that?
去个大家都认识我的地方
Why would I ever go where everybody knows who I am
然后被众人讪笑吗
and be publicly humiliated?
我知道这事情很煎熬
I know it will be hard for you,
但我保证你会不虚此行
but I promise it'll be worth it.
在拍卖会上
There's one thing at that auction
有件我很在乎很想你拥有的东西
that I really care about that I want you to have.
什么东西
What?
是我婴儿期的那幅画像吗
The painting of me as a baby?
还是那个根据我五岁时样子做的雕像
The sculpture of me as a five-year-old?
或是按照我十四岁样子织的壁毯
the tapestry of me at 14?
我有张七岁时 被警察当犯人画的素描像
I have a pretty good police sketch of me at seven.
我想你们去拍卖会
I want you two to go there
买回你骑着栗宝得到的马术纪念杯
and get the loving cup you won jumping with chestnut.
我知道那奖杯对你多重要
I know how much that meant to you.
就算我能够忍受出席的痛苦
Even if I could bring myself to go through all that,
但我们真得省下每一分钱来用于生意
we need every penny we have for the cupcake business.
告诉我爸爸 麦克斯
Tell him, Max.
马丁 你知道我愿为你做任何事
Martin, you know I'd do anything for you.
任何事
Anything.
但我们俩真的一穷二白了
But it's true. We're broke.
-时间到了 -老爸 这是真的
- Time is up. - Seriously, daddy,
我用肥皂包装盒来当钱包呢
I use the box our soap comes in as a wallet.
天啊 这也太凄凉心酸了
Man, that is hard to hear.
麦克斯 你也是我的好女孩吧
Max, you're my girl, right?
我是吗
Am I?
我希望你想办法弄回那个奖杯
I want you to find a way to get that cup.
无论她怎么抗拒 一定要买回来
No matter what she says, make sure she gets that cup.
跟得上吗
You follow me?
你想我跟你进去啊
You want me to follow you?
狱方会允许我进去吗
Can I even go back there?
小姐 您不能
No, you can't, Miss.
哦 你是说跟上你的思维
Oh, follow you, like follow your thought.
那东西对她很重要
It's important for her,
而且对你们都很重要
and it's important for the both of you
对你们的未来很重要
For your futures, all right?
弄到那奖杯 回答我 我要你弄什么呢
Get the cup. What are you getting?
那奖杯吗 马丁
The cup, Martin?
我爱你们 两个小甜心
I love you, sweethearts.
老爸我也爱你
Love you too, daddy.
别担心 我们会弄回那奖杯的
And don't worry, we'll get that cup.
我才不会去买那奖杯
I'm not getting that cup.
什么 那你干嘛答应他你会买
What? Then why did you say you would?
不可以拒绝在坐牢的人啊
You can't tell a man in prison "no".
他会用皮带上吊的
He'll hang himself with his belt.
你都碰过两次了
It happened to you twice already.
我们一定得去买回那个奖杯
We have to go get that cup.
为什么
Why?
奖杯里有钱
There's money in the cup.
这话什么意思
What are you talking about?
他说你的未来需要那个奖杯
He said we needed it for our future,
然后眨了眼
then he winked.
不是暗指有钱 就是他在对我放电
It was either that, or he was hitting on me,
坦白说 那样也不赖
which, I'm not gonna lie, I wouldn't hate.
他为什么要藏钱在奖杯里啊 神探南茜
How would he even hide money in a cup, Nancy Drew?
那纪念杯长什么样子
Well, what does a loving cup look like?
跟保龄球奖杯差不多吗
Is it like a bowling trophy?
你居然贬低我的奖杯
How dare you.
是不是有个木头底座啦
Does it have, like, a wood base?
没错了 我以前也藏大麻在我妈的奖杯底座
Yup, I used to hide my stash in my mother's bowling trophy,
你觉得一个能够想出方法
And you're telling me the man who invented a way
骗尽大半个纽约的天才
to defraud most of New York isn't as clever
想不到十二岁嗑药妹就能想出的法子吗
as a stoned 12-year-old with a butter knife?
他都不听我说小蛋糕
Well, it was weird how it was all about the cup
只顾着说奖杯 的确有点古怪
and so little about the pumpkin spice cupcake.
对吧
Right?
而且你觉得那位
And you don't think your father
愿意花钱来做你的雕像
who spent a fortune to turn you into a sculpture,
可能还是裸体的老爸
presumably nude, wouldn't try to figure out a way
不会想办法给女儿留后路吗
to take care of his only daughter?
他是个犯罪天才
The man's a criminal genius,
他想到这个替你未来留后路的方法
and he found a way to put money for your future in the cup,
所以他才要我千里迢迢地过来谈
and clearly, that's why he dragged me out to prison,
因为他知道你会听我的话
because he knows you'll do what I say
因为我是你的老大
'cause I'm the boss of you,
而且很快还会升级到当你的继母
and pretty soon, I'm gonna be your stepmom.
你的意思我明白了
I hear what you're saying,
但我有个重要的问题
but I just have one big question.
要花多少钱来标这纪念杯吗
How much are we willing to bid?
不是 是我得易容
No, about my disguise.
我可以扮个褐法妞 但要留刘海吗
I know I'm a brunette, but do I have bangs?
我要两份 一份给我
Actually, I need two: one for me,
一份给我的朋友佐伊·丹斯切尔
and one for my friend Zooey Deschanel.
-干嘛 你看起来像她啊 -谁不像她啊
- What? You look like her. - Everybody does.
最省置装费 又有人愿意"睡"的打扮了
It's the least expensive look you can do and still get laid.
这些是储物间里的东西 都好多年没见到了
God, this is from storage. I haven't seen it in years.
你们拥有这些衣柜
Wow, you had all these closets,
你们家族里真的没人是基佬吗
and no one in your family is gay?
这路易十六的衣柜 以前是放在我的游戏房的
Look! It's the Louie the XVI I used to have in my playroom.
以前我都跟我表弟彼得一起爬进去
My cousin Peter and I used to climb in here
然后重演法国大革命
and play French Revolution.
我扮演玛丽·安托瓦内特
I'd be Marie Antoinette,
然后他会帮我把头发弄上假髻
and he'd help me put my hair up in a high chignon.
我突然觉得他老婆好可怜啊
Oh, now I'm feeling bad for his wife.
那个奖杯会放哪里呢
So where do you think the cup is?
看看那边吧
Let's look over there.
这是避暑别墅的东西
Oh, this is from the summer house.
麦克斯 你听过有句话叫
Max, you know the expression
"含着银汤匙出生吗"
"born with a silver spoon in your mouth"?
这是我的
This is mine.
小姐 请勿触碰
Miss, do not handle that.
请您立刻放下
I'm asking you to put it down right now.
你最好注意一下你的态度
Hey, you might wanna relax the attitude.
你觉得我朋友 詹妮弗·洛芙·休伊特
You really think my friend Jennifer Love Hewitt,
这位国际电影明星与生活台巨星
international movie and LifeTime channel superstar,
会偷人家用过的汤匙吗
is gonna steal a used spoon?
抱歉 前面没认出来
Sorry, I didn't recognize you.
现在认出来了
Now I see it.
我不是佐伊·丹斯切尔吗
I thought I was Zooey Deschanel.
半斤八两啦
Eh, six of one.
好莱坞褐发女星都长得差不多
All you hollywood brunettes look alike.
先生女士们 拍卖会即将开始
The auction is starting, ladies and gentlemen.
你好吗 麦克斯
Hi, Max.
好高兴来这里
I'm so excited to be here.
你好 卡洛琳
Oh, hello, Caroline .
苏菲 我为我那天的行为道歉
Sophie, I apologize for the other day.
我那时心情太紧张了 不是有意的
I was really tense, and I didn't mean it.
我觉得你的风格十分独特
I think you have a unique sense of style.
少少的布料 大大的美丽
You do so much with so little fabric.
的确
I do...
看来你听我的话 去看波兰版《时尚》杂志啦
And I see you took my advice and got Polish Vogue.
这样真好
How nice is this?
我们终于开始浪漫约会
We are finally on a romantic date.
我们刚在高档餐厅吃完饭
We just came from lunch at Rainbow Room,
我也穿着我最好的一件飞乐运动服
And I'm wearing my best Fila tracksuit.
现在他要买金闪闪的东西给我了
Yah, now, he's going to buy me something golden.
没错 我就想要全身被黄金覆盖
Yah, I want to be covered in gold.
想要个黄金淋浴
I want a golden shower.
想想 如果我是个纪念杯
Let's see. If I was a loving cup,
我会在哪里
where would I be?
某个你体内被塞了很多钞票的地方
Some place with a lot of cash shoved up inside you.
你觉得里面会有多少钱啊
How much do you think is in there?
看嘛 奖杯的木头底座大概这么大
Well, let's see. The wooden base of the cup is about this big,
你可以在口香糖罐里塞2万
and I know you can get 20,000 in an Altoids tin,
而这底座有它的三倍的大
and this is about three times that size,
就表示装了6万吧
So 60,000.
就跟一百万一样多啊
That's like a million dollars!
再一个小时 我就有6万块了吗
So I could have $60,000 in an hour?
是我们 我们就有
Well, we. We could have it.
我说了"我"吗 真奇怪
Did I say I? How weird.
成交
And sold.
东西都被你买走啦
Wow, you're getting everything.
是啊 都被我们买走了
Yes, we are.
对不对啊 泡菜小姐
Aren't we, Miss Pickle?
我叫哈米斯·麦克唐纳
I'm Hamish Mcdonough, by the way.
我叫麦克斯 她是我朋友凯蒂·赫尔姆斯
Oh, I'm Max, and this is my friend Katie Holmes.
我们不会说出去的
We won't speak of it...
不过我想说 离得好
But I just have to say: well done!
如果哪天你需要什么 千万别客气
And if you ever need anything, don't hesitate.
你有自己的店啊
Oh, you have your own shop?
"二人世界"古董店
"Just the two of us" Antiques.
是你跟泡菜小姐吗
Is that you and Miss Pickle?
亲爱的 我又不是疯子
No, dear, I'm not insane.
下一件要拍卖的物品
Next item for auction:
十九世纪的象牙黄金床边小桌
A 19th century ivory and gold bedside table,
再说一次
Oh, say it again.
有点不一般的要求 不过我再说一遍
This is highly unorthodox, but I shall repeat the item.
十九世纪的象牙黄金床边小桌
A 19th century gold and ivory bedside table--
我是个"性"福的男人 对吧
I'm a very lucky man, yes?
这间物品的起标价是
We start the opening bid on this item
5万块
at $50,000.
我退出
I'm out.
-5万 -这里
- 50,000. - Here.
有人出6万吗
Do I hear 60,000?
-6万 -这位先生出6万
- 60,000! - 60,000 over here.
-有人愿意出7万吗 -我
- Do I hear 70,000? - Here.
-7万 -有人要出8万吗
- 70,000. - Do I hear 80,000?
有的 我出
Yes, you do!
8万一次 两次
80,000 going once, going twice,
成交
Sold.
哈米斯 你威震全场啊
Hamish, you killed it.
那是哟
Yolo!
下一件要拍卖的物品
And the next item up for bid
是一个镀银锡制纪念杯
is a silver-plated tin loving cup,
卡洛琳·钱宁所拥有过的物品
Property of Caroline Channing.
你觉得这东西会喊到多高的价
How much do you think this is going to go for?
这类东西起伏大 但本身都没实际价值
Kitsch is always a wild card, but it has no real value.
没实际价值 拜托哦
No real value? Please.
那我是在没人看好的情况下赢来的
I won that when no one thought I could.
我身染肺炎 雨中骑栗宝跳过十四个栅栏
I jumped 14 hurdles in the rain with walking pneumonia.
这可是相当价值的
It's worth something.
是啊 价值来自里面的钞票
Yeah, 'cause it has money in it.
起标价50块
We start the bidding at $50.
先生 加价幅度是10块钱
Sir, it's in increments of $10.
那我退出
Then, I'm out.
抱歉嘛 吃高档餐厅把我的钱都榨干了
Sorry, the Rainbow Room really sucked me dry.
你猜猜我身上现在哪里也很"干"
Hm, guess what else is pretty dry right now?
有人出60吗
Do I hear 60?
你在干嘛 你不是说不值钱吗
What are you doing? You said it had no real value.
是啊 但你想象一下
I know, but wouldn't it be camp
拍一张泡菜小姐用奖杯洗澡的照片
to see Miss Pickle taking a bath in that
来当圣诞卡 一定超可爱
for my christmas card?
有人出70吗
Do I hear 70?
我的奖杯不是狗狗的澡盆
My cup is not a puppy bath.
放弃吧小姐们 我乃竞价小贱哥
Back out now, ladies. I'm a paddle bitch.
我还是贱人贱贱姐呢 100
Well, I'm a bitch bitch. 100.
-175 -哈米斯想斗
- 175. - Hamish came to play.
我们斗死他 我处女膜是练马给练没了的呢
So did we, I broke my hymen getting that thing.
所以才叫纪念杯吗
Is that why it's called a loving cup?
200 我出200
200. I have 200.
有人出225吗
Do I hear 225?
听我说 哈米斯
Look, Hamish.
我知道你对我平常拿来说服人的"本钱"
I know you have no interest in what I would normally
没有兴趣
offer you to get what I want.
话别说太早 62岁前我一直"男女通吃"
Don't be so sure. I was bisexual till I was 62.
凯蒂·赫尔姆斯真的很想要这东西
Look, Katie Holmes really wants this,
你看她经历了那么多苦难
and she's been through a lot.
好吧 你们拿去 我退出
True. It's yours. I'm out.
200块一次 两次
200 going once, going twice.
成交 爽啊 我有钱啦
Sold. Yes, I'm rich!
你又说了"我"吗
Did you just say "I'm"?
是你听错了吧
I think you're hearing me wrong.
在我们把钱花在生意之前
Okay, before we use all this money on the business,
先去度个假吧 你说如何
we should take a vacation. How 'bout it?
你 我 栗宝 水上摩托车
You, me, Chestnut, jet skis.
拿出来吧
Okay, here we go.
别别别 别现在打开
No, no, no. Don't open it now.
这里有摄像头
There are cameras here.
那我们去那边打开吧
We can just go over there and open it
就去你跟你的娘炮亲戚
Right next to that thing where you
玩变装游戏的那衣柜旁边
and your little queen cousin played dress-up.
说真的 我当年怎么没看出来
Seriously, how could I not have known that?
我们玩牛仔大战印第安人
When we played cowboys and Indians,
他总是扮演印第安化妆师
he played the Indian's makeup artist.
我得说 麦克斯
I have to say, Max,
能在拥有一点钱真的很开心
it'll be nice to have some money again,
但更开心的是 你看到了我爸的为人
but what's really nice is that now you see who my father is,
一个虽然有不少缺点
a man who, despite all of his flaws,
但是总是想方设法
never stopped thinking about what he could do
照顾他宝贝女儿的好父亲
to take care of his little girl.
居然是空的
It's empty?
那个老混蛋
Son of a bitch.
马丁 我们有个问题
Martin, we just have one question.
钱呢
Where's the money?
抱歉 你说什么
I'm sorry, what?
钱 在哪里
Where's...the money?
什么
What?
她再问你钱藏哪去了
She's asking where the money is.
哦 什么钱啊
Oh! Uh, what money?
奖杯里的钱啊 老爸
The money in the cup, daddy.
你为我的未来所预留的钱啊
The money you hid in the cup that was supposed to be for my future?
我的6万块在哪里
Where's my 60 grand?
给所有可能在读我唇的人
Which, for anyone who might be watching my lips,
我们是要拿那笔钱去做公益
we were going to give all to charity.
宝贝 你怎么会觉得我有藏钱呢
Sweetheart, why do you think I would hide money,
虽然我被关就是因为藏了钱
Besides the fact I'm here for hiding money?
这可能是我的错
Well, that might have been my fault.
老爸 这不是她的错
No, it's not her fault, daddy.
是你的
It's yours.
你本应该好好照顾我 可你却没有
You were supposed to take care of me, and you didn't.
你从没为我想过
You didn't think about me at all,
不只是我 你伤了那么多人
And it's not just me. You hurt a lot of people.
你想过他们的感受吗
Do you ever even think about them?
有啊
Yes, I do.
我现在每日每夜地想
Now, every day,
但我也想到我对你做的那些事
but I also think about what I did to you
整天都在想
every day, all day.
我是说 以前
I mean, back then,
当我知道如何捞不劳而获的钱时
when I figured out a way to get free money,
我脑子里想的全是钱
all I could think about was the money.
嗯哼
I hear that.
可我是真心想送你的未来一份礼 宝贝
But I really did wanna give you something for your future, sweetheart,
所以我才请麦克斯来确保
which is why I asked Max to make sure
你会拿到那个奖杯
that you got that cup.
虽然只是个锡奖杯
And I know it's only tin,
但那是我能给你最有价值的东西了
but it's the most valuable thing I could give you,
因为它能提醒你
because it'll remind you
无论境况有多糟糕
that no matter how hard the circumstances,
你都能跨过任何的难关
you could get over any hurdle,
即便是我给你带来的困境 你也能大步跨过
even the ones I put in front of you.
好吧 我们该走了 时间到了
Okay, well, we should go. Our time's up.
这么快要走啊 你才刚到呢
Yeah, but--what? You just got here.
我今天已经听够了
Well, I think I'm done for today.
我一直都害怕有天你会用这眼神看我
Boy, I've dreaded the day you looked at me like this.
今天真的看到了 比我想象中还难受
Now that it's here, it's even worse.
我只希望有一天
I only hope that one day
你会换个眼神看我
you could look at me again
用你赢得奖杯那时的眼神看我
the way you did the day you won that cup.
宝贝 我爱你
I love you, honey.
老爸 我也爱你
I love you too, daddy.
抱歉
Oh. Sorry.
你是对她说
You meant her.
下周见吗
See you next week?
有老爸的日子也不好过呀
Wow, having a father is rough.
-你没事吧 -会没事的
- Are you okay? - I will be,
无论其他人怎么想
Because despite what everyone else may think,
他都不止是个贼 他是我的父亲
he's not just a thief. He's my father,
我爱他
And I love him.
不知道这能不能让你觉得安慰
Look, if it's any consolation,
但我看出他为何会有今日了
I now see how that could've happened to him.
我不会原谅他
I'm not condoning it,
只是我懂为何别人会被拐了
but I see how people can get caught up,
但我还在生气 气下周
'cause I am pissed as hell that next week